[{"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075042", "chunk": 0, "question": "bicycle", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Fahrrad", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075120", "chunk": 0, "question": "cat", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Katze", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075146", "chunk": 0, "question": "dog", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Der Hund", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075164", "chunk": 0, "question": "\uace0\uc591\uc774", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die koreansiche Katze", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075180", "chunk": 0, "question": "flute", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Fl\u00f6te", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672376", "chunk": 1, "question": "\uace0\uc591\uc774", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die koreanisch", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672443", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ub9d0", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Pferd", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672466", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ubc30", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Wasser", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672484", "chunk": 1, "question": "\uc9d1", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Haus", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933695", "chunk": 2, "question": "rose", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Rose", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933771", "chunk": 2, "question": "guitar", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Gitarre", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933795", "chunk": 2, "question": "man", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Der Mann", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933814", "chunk": 2, "question": "women", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Frau", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672504", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ubb3c", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Wasser", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:55:57.075202", "chunk": 0, "question": "newspaper", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Zeitung", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:08.672522", "chunk": 1, "question": "BigMac", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "BigMax", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933832", "chunk": 2, "question": "trombone", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Posaune", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-20 12:56:27.933848", "chunk": 2, "question": "trousers", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Hose", "learned": false}]